<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="add">Add a new item</string>
    <string name="add_cat">Add category</string>
    <string name="app_name">WeShould</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_add">Add a category\n  **Every list item will have a name field.  If mappable is selected, an address field will be available when adding an item and if phoneable is selected, a phone number entry field will be available when adding an item.  It is not necessary to add  these entry fields when creating a category.\n  1 - Enter the name of the category you wish to create by clicking inside the first text entry area.\n  2 - When finished, press done on the keypad or press the device \'Back\' button.\n  3 - For each field you would like to add for your category…\n    A - Press the \'Add Field\' button in the lower left corner of the screen.\n    B - Enter the name of the field by clicking inside the \'Field Name\' text entry area.\n    C - When finished, press \'Done\' on the keypad or press the device \'Back\' button.\n    D - You can change this entry by clicking inside the text box at any time before pressing the \'Save\' button.\n    E - Press the triangle in the entry box below name to change the type of field you wish to create.\n    F - The popup window will display your choices.  The green dot inside the circle to the right of the choices indicates the type currently selected.\n    G - If the type you want is already selected, press the \'Back\' button on our device.  Otherwise, select the type you want by pressing the circle next to the type. This window will close upon making a selection.\n    H - You can change this selection by pressing the triangle at any time before pressing the \'Save\' button.\n    I - You may delete a created field by pressing the \'-\' button to the left of the field name.\n    J - More fields can be added by returning to Step A\n  4 - Press the \'Save\' button when finished adding and editing fields.\n\nAdd a tag\n  1 - Enter the tag name into the field provided.\n  2 - When the name is complete, press \'Done\' on the keypad or the device \'Back\' button.\n  3 - Press the \'Save\' button when finished.\n\nAdd a list item\n  1 - Select the category of the item being entered.\n  2 - Click inside the \'name\' box and type the name of the item.\n  3 - When the name is complete, press the device back button to exit the entry window, or press \'next\' on the keypad to move to the next field.\n  4 - Enter any information you you would like to add into the other fields by clicking on the field box and typing the information.\n      **Fields marked with a \'*\' are required.\n  5 - Press the \'Save\' button when finished.</string>
    <string name="help_edit">Edit a category\n    **Note: The field names and types of a category cannot be changed.\n  1 - Select the field you wish to change by touching the text entry area.\n\nEdit a list item\n    **The category of an item cannot be changed.  To view the item in a different list, you may add a tag to the item and view tag lists, or you can delete the item and recreate it using a new category.\n  1 - ..\n  2 - ..\n  3 - ..\n\nEdit a tag\n  1 - ..\n  2 - ..\n  3 - ..\n\n</string>
    <string name="help_home">Add a category, list item, or tag\n  1 - Press the device menu button and select the appropriate ‘Add’ button.\n      See the Add help page for more information.\n\nEdit a list item\n  1 - Select the item you wish to edit from the list to go to the item iformation page.\n  2 - Press the edit button on the bottom of that page.\n  3 - See the item information or edit help pages for further information.\n\nView a category list\n  1 - If tag names are displayed in the horizontal tabs, press the device menu button and select ‘View by Categories’.\n      *The tab of the current list being displayed is highlighted.  A different category list can be viewed by pressing the tab of the desired list.\n\nView a tag list\n  1 - If category names are displayed in the horizontal tabs, press the device menu button and select ‘View by Tags.\n      *The tab of the current tag being displayed is highlighted.  All items tagged with the current tagged with the curret tag are shown in the current list.  A different tag list can be viewed by pressing the tab of the desired list.\n\nMove an item to a different list\n  1 - See Edit a Category on the edit help page.</string>
    <string name="help_text">Welcome to WeShould!  This is the help text!</string>
    <string name="no_cat">No categories exist.  Please press the menu button and add a category.</string>
</resources>