<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="add">Add a new item</string>
    <string name="add_cat">Add category</string>
    <string name="app_name">WeShould</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_add">Add a category\n\n**Every list item will have a name field.  It is not necessary to add a name field when creating a category.\n\nSpecial Fields, if checked, will provide the following field types when entering a list item..\n\nAddress - an address field for pin placement on the map.\n\nPhone number - a phone number that can be clicked to call\n\nURL - A web address that can be clicked to open in the browser.\n\n1 - Enter the name of the category you wish to create by clicking inside the first text entry area and typing on the device keypad.\n\n2 - When finished, press \'done\' on the keypad or press the device \'Back\' button.\n\n3 - For each field you would like to add for your category…\n\nA - Press the device menu button and select \'Add Field\'\n\nB - Enter the name of the field by clicking inside the \'Field name\' text entry area.\n\nC - When finished, press \'Done\' on the keypad or press the device \'Back\' button.\n\nD - You can change previous entries by clicking inside the text box at any time before saving the created category.\n\nE - Press the triangle in the entry box \'TextField\' to change the type of field you wish to create.\n\nF - The popup window will display your choices.  The green dot inside the circle to the right of the choices indicates the type currently selected.\n\nG - Select the type you want by pressing the circle next to the type, or click the device \'Back\' button to exit. This window will close upon making a selection.\n\nH - You can change this selection by pressing the triangle at any time before saving the category.\n\nI - You may delete a created field by pressing the \'-\' button to the left of the field name.\n\nJ - More fields can be added by returning to Step A\n\n4 - Press the device menu button and select \'Save\' when finished adding and editing fields.\n\n\n***Final Release Feature***\nAdd a tag\n\n1 - Enter the tag name into the field provided.\n  2 - When the name is complete, press \'Done\' on the keypad or the device \'Back\' button.\n  3 - Press the \'Save\' button when finished.\n\n</string>
    <string name="help_home">Add a category or list item\n\n1 - Press the device menu button and select the appropriate \'Add\' button.\n\n2 - If adding an item, select the category of the item to be entered from the popup list.\n\n**See the Add help page for more information.\n\n\nEdit a list item\n\n1 - Long click the item you wish to edit.\n\n2 - Select \'Edit\' from the popup menu.\n\n**See the Edit help pages for further information.\n\n\nView a category list\n\n1 - If tag names are displayed in the horizontal tabs, press the device menu button and select \'View by Categories\'.\n\n**The tab of the current list being displayed is highlighted.  A different category list can be viewed by pressing the tab of the desired list.\n\n\nView a tag list\n\n1 - If category names are displayed in the horizontal tabs, press the device menu button and select \'Sort by Tags\'.\n\n**The tab of the current tag being displayed is highlighted.  A different tag list can be viewed by pressing the tab of the desired list.\n\n\nDelete a category or tag\n\n1 - Select the tab of the category or tag you wish to delete.\n\n2 - When the list is empty, click the \'Delete\' button.\n\n\nZoom map in\n\n1 - Touch the map with two fingers and move them apart.\n\n\nZoom map out\n\n1 - Touch the map with two fingers and move them toward each other.\n\n\nCenter map on current location\n\n1 - Press the blue button in the top left corner of the map.\n\n\nView Item on map\n\n1 - Tap an item to adjust the map to show that item\'s location and your current location.\n\n2 - Tap the selected item again to zoom in and center on that item only.\n\n**Select item is the yellow pin.\n\n\nBackup your lists\n\n1 - Press the menu button and select \'Backup\'.\n\n**Previous backups will be overwritten.\n\n\nRestore from backup\n\n1 - Press the menu button and select \'Restore\'.\n\n**All categories, tags, and items will be deleted and the contents of the last backup will replace them.\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="help_edit">Adding a list item\n\n1 - Click inside the \'Name\' box and type the name of the item.\n\n2 - When the name is complete, press the device \'back\' button to exit the entry window.\n\n3 - Enter any information you you would like to add into the other fields by clicking on the field box and typing the information.  URL, address, and phone number fields should be filled in complete, as they are used to make calls, open the browser, and map addresses.\n\n4 - Press the device menu button and select \'Save\' when finished.\n\n\nEditing an item\n\n1 - Select the field you wish to change by touching the text entry area.\n\n2 - When finished typing, press the device \'back\' button.\n\n3 - When all edits are complete, press the device \'menu\' button and select \'Save\'\n\n**Note: The field names and types of an item and its category cannot be changed.  To view the item in a different list, you may add a tag to the item and view tag lists, or you can delete the item and recreate it using a new category.\n\n\nSet a tag to an item\n\n1 - To set an item, you have to go into editscreen of an item.  At the bottom of each edit page, there will be place to click to edit which tag should be assocaite with the tag.  \n\n2 - After click, a popup box will prompt user to click \'create new tag\' to create a new cusotm tag, \'set tag\' to set existing tag to the item.\n\n3 - You can have multiple tags associates with an item. \n\n For each tag, you can select the color to display on the map when using \'sort by tag\' option on the map screen menu.</string>
    <string name="help_text">Welcome to WeShould!  This is the help text!</string>
    <string name="no_cat">No categories exist.  Please press the menu button and add a category.</string>
    <string name="help_information">Special fields\n\nPhone number - press the number to call\n\nURL - press the web address to open in the browser</string>
    <string name="delete_item">Delete Item</string>
    <string name="delete_item_confirm">Are you sure you wish to delete this item?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="help_splash">Select one of the accounts you have associated with this device. This account you choose will be used to send and receive referrals to and from other WeShould users. You only have to log in once. We will remember you next time ;)</string>
</resources>